<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<!--
  ! whitespaces
-->
<info>
  <newwizard hello="5">
    <site1>
Enter a name for your project and the path to the directory where it is to be
saved. Normally, the working directory is the root for all project and language files.
    </site1>
    <site2>
If a reference (language) file is specified, the wizard can collect some other language
files, automatically. Additionally you can insert (already existing) language files, edit
some settings or remove unused files.
    </site2>
  </newwizard>
  <codeinsight>
    <site1>
The Codeinsight feature parse a set of source files and can extract
the translation-keys from it. Please enter the path of the sources and choose
a source parser (every parser has specific properties).
    </site1>
  </codeinsight>
  <options>
    <defaultProject>
These settings are the default values for every new project. You can change the
project settings at the project properties dialog.
    </defaultProject>
    <font>
Here you can define your preferred font for the language components (e.g.
the table). Attention, many fonts can't represent all characters of all
languages correctly. At the "supported languages" box are examples of
different supported classes of languages (only non-latin and incomplete).
    </font>
  </options>
  <newlanguage>
    <site1>
Please insert the ISO 639 two-character code for the language. Additional you can specify the
iso code for a country and/or a variant.If you press the '?' key, a simple dialog is opened,
which can help to select the correct iso code.
    </site1>
    <site2>
Here you can make some file settings, like the the encoding. It is nessesary for the right
interpretation of the single characters of the file content. The "java utf" encoding is the
standard encoding, it is a combination of ISO 8859-1 character encoding and java escape
sequences like \u0045.
    </site2>
    <warning1>
Warning! The encoding option will be ignored until the WYSIWYG option is enabled.
    </warning1>
  </newlanguage>
  <savelanguage>
    <head>
Please choose one or more languages for saving.
    </head>
  </savelanguage>

  <checkversion title="Check for a new Version">
    <summary>
This dialog examines whether a newer version of @APPLICATION_NAME@ is present on the @PROJECT_HOST@ server.
    </summary>
  </checkversion>

  <validations title="Validation Wizard">
    <summary>
This wizard can perform some simple checks.
    </summary>
  </validations>

</info>
